{
    "subject": "resource/Rich_Relations_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Frances_Grant",
    "human_readable": "The film Rich Relations stars Frances Grant.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8949891328811646,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Frances Grant's role in Rich Relations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8302491307258606,
            "question": "What is the name of the film starring Frances Grant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8085539937019348,
            "question": "Who stars in the film Rich Relations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7114056348800659,
            "question": "Who directed the film Rich Relations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6921147704124451,
            "question": "Are there any other films starring Frances Grant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6069389581680298,
            "question": "Is Frances Grant an actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4013102650642395,
            "question": "What is the plot of Rich Relations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.387845516204834,
            "question": "What genre is the film Rich Relations likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38781264424324036,
            "question": "When was the film Rich Relations released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2132086604833603,
            "question": "Where can I watch Rich Relations?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film Rich Relations stars Frances Grant.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3519_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the film Rich Relations released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3519_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Rich Relations likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3519_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of Rich Relations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3519_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3519_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3519_149.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3519_155.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3519_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3519_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3519_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3519_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3519_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3519_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3519_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context mentions that Frances Grant played the role of Nancy Tilton in the film \"Rich Relations\" (1937), which supports the statement that the film \"Rich Relations\" stars Frances Grant."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}